Welcome friends to
Tencent Video's original
mature love observation reality show
"Half-Mature Lovers" Season 4
Nice to see you again
Welcome to our new friends this time
Grasping every stage rhythm
and easily capturing the love electrocardiogram
Xia Zhiguang
This name
That's impressive, Guangguang
No
I want to ask
Did you watch our previous show?
Yes, I did
It was wonderful
Which relationship impressed you the most?
Teacher Hou and Wowo
Why?
Tell us more
Actually, I think
In relationships, sincerity is the ultimate weapon
And some of his words
And some of his actions
Really touched me, yes
Especially his introduction
That the world of Truman is fake
But Truman is real
It feels like
Maybe this show is staged
But my love for you is real
Yes
So it really touched me
Guangguang, you are a pure love warrior
Easily moved by
Such touching words, right?
Yes, Teacher Xu too
Alright, let's see today
the duel between two pure love warriors
I would like to ask
about a guy named Teacher Luo
Are you talking about this one?
Yes
And the one who was self-deprecating in the car
Suddenly
And when the new guest came in
he was singing
Then that look in his eyes
That expression, I can remember it for a lifetime
Really
What expression?
Let's recreate it
It felt like peeking through a door crack, right?
I think Luo Junfan in the last episode
had many memorable scenes
One was given to him by Xiao Jie
How to introduce Luo Junfan
His profession is
an online sales person
I burst out laughing at that time
And there was another part
when Xia Xia was drawing
and suddenly received a task
His laugh directly
Yes
Yes, he thought he was the only one favored
but actually, everyone was equally favored
Turns out, the clown was himself
Yes, you noticed the details well
Teacher Luo is here
He is our comedic seasoning
Yes
Teacher Luo contributed many memorable moments
Okay
The New Year is coming soon
Then everyone can see
everyone is actively preparing for the New Year's Eve party
making preparations
Yes
Next, let's quickly go to the Half-Cooked House
to see their New Year's Eve
and what will happen
Looking forward to it
It's a real tea party
It's so exciting
Are we all just kneeling here like this?
And here is a letter from Wowo
A letter to everyone
Dear everyone
Happy New Year
Because there are still some official duties
So it's very unfortunate
I can't celebrate New Year's Eve with everyone
The pain of a working person
But my heart is with everyone
I infused my thoughts
Into the macarons
I hope everyone eats them
And has a sweet new year
I will rush back to the team as soon as I finish my work
Love, Wowo
Thank you, Wowo
Teacher Hou can't smile
Disappointed
Actually, I am a person
Who really likes celebrating New Year's Eve
When I found out she couldn't
Celebrate New Year's Eve with us
I felt a bit down
So why don't we start with Wowo's
Macarons
How did we start dining already
The show hasn't started yet and we're already eating
Here
Come, look over there
Three, two, one
Okay
Is everyone doing the scissors hand gesture?
This is a characteristic of people our age
Teacher Luo will start the show
Okay
Dear audience friends
Good evening, everyone
He's doing a great job as the host here
Yes, I think so too
Wait for me a moment
No, wait a moment
Come
Three, two, one, go
Distinguished audience members here and in front of the screen
Everyone
Good evening
It's starting
Welcome everyone
Welcome everyone to our Half-Ripe House
The live broadcast of the 2024 to 2025 New Year's Eve party
I am your host, Liang Tian
How is everyone
Actually, 2024 for us
is a year of striving
is a year of harvest
This is meant for the leaders to hear, right?
Being able to be with our Half-Mature House
all the outstanding boys and girls
gathered together
should be the most intense New Year's Eve I've felt in the past decade
really felt very strongly about this New Year's Eve
Here, I personally
thank all the friends present
Thank you
This host is so professional
It really feels like watching a New Year's Eve concert
Let's look at the first program list
What are you singing?
There's a Soul App here
It has a great group chat party feature
Yes, it can share interests
You can also listen to songs and sing
Impressive
Create a party
Create a room
And there are many different songs inside
I want to sing this one
I happen to like it
Pretty good, okay
Come on, any other microphone masters, come over
New Year's Eve song library, Soul has enough
Let's do it together
Come on, quickly, let's start "Calla Lily Love"
This song is so cheerful
Don't mess with me
Add some dance steps or something
New Year's Eve parties are quite fun.
It's just friends hanging out.
It's about enjoying the atmosphere.
Today, I'll become a mind-reading master.
From 1 to 20.
Pick a number.
36.
I said from 1 to 20.
Great.
I envy this kind of atmosphere
So happy
Alright, whose (program) is next? What?
Come
Yonghao will accompany
Let's welcome
A song that represents
My deep blessings to everyone
I hope everyone in the new year
Can find someone
To have a love that never loses connection with you
I think everyone is very talented
Really
This singing is so beautiful
The accompaniment is amazing
This is my talent show
Alright
Since that's the case
We can start listening to the copyrighted music, right?
Let's welcome with applause
I can help you play
Alright
The sheet music is there
Here
This is the song Su Nan revised for a whole day
Really, from dawn to dusk
Really
Didn't even go to buy fireworks
I don't even remember the lyrics I wrote myself
I'll open QQ Music
Original song
Yes, the song she wrote the lyrics for herself
So cute
Not bad
Why does it feel like
we're college classmates hanging out together?
Yes
And this scene reminds me of when they first met
They first met sitting on a bench, playing the piano and singing
Yes
They are actually very in sync
So cute
It's a very cheerful little song
But I think it's perfect for the Half-Ripe Cottage
Especially suitable
So suitable
Thank you, everyone
I hope everyone has a happy New Year
Happy New Year
Thank you, teacher, for playing the piano
Played well
We also have a poem
We both have a poem
Poetry recitation
This poem is his
This is his
How come? Did he write it?
No, we both carefully selected it today
We selected it
It feels like everyone has gone through
many different changes
And no matter what our relationship is
when we leave the cottage
it will be a friendship
or a romantic relationship
But I believe each relationship will
bring us some meaningful changes
So this poem is related to that
Can Su Nan help us with the accompaniment?
I can play for you
Sure
Come on, let's start
Is this Luo Junfan translating?
I think he is actually quite cute.
He just quietly glanced at Liang Tian twice.
The last thing he said to her was,
I guessed it was an English recitation.
Brother
There are flowers.
Come on, brother
He is playing the piano
Playing the piano
He plays the piano
Look at this somewhat familiar person
How many are there in all of China
But only a dozen of us
Were chosen to be here
I think this fate is very rare
So let's play one
"This World Has So Many People"
I really like this song
Another song we can sing together
I can
with so many good friends and new friends
celebrate the New Year together
I am very excited
I also feel very warm
I also prepared for everyone
some small gifts
So many
This is for Kaka
And I have a blessing written below
I hope that when your energy is exhausted
You don't always have to be happy
Sister
Help
I hope this time
Our precious experience
Can give you a special experience
So you don't feel like
A stray cat
No longer wandering
Thank you
Xia Xia is a
Very, very caring
And considerate girl
In her drawings
She added many small elements
Like what we wore when we first met
Including the colors we use to describe ourselves
And a phrase she wants to give us
They are all quite fitting
And they are words we need to hear
It feels like we have her affirmation
Xia Xia's gesture is very warm
She drew a picture for everyone
So Xia Xia was always drawing
She hid each drawing for New Year's
To surprise everyone
Everyone's image in her heart is amazing
I'm so curious about what she drew for Luo Junfan
And the words I give to you are
You might be happier if you don't hide in your shell
Like a raccoon in its shell
He says he's a little panda
Yes
If you don't wrap yourself too tightly
Someone might actually come in and understand you
The first impression is that you are humorous and interesting
It's not stressful to be around you
You like reading alone
Yet you do the most lively work on site
Glass crispy pigeon
Will find ways to liven up the atmosphere
Consider this as their own responsibility
It must be very hard
At that time, I felt
This guy might not be as
happy as he appears
So I added this eggshell
Xia Xia was seriously watching him
Really
I hope you can come out of the shell you built
After you come out, you will be
able to genuinely
show this happiness and joy
Don't hide anything
I think she has a lot to say
that really touched my heart
I am also very grateful to her
for making such a painting for me
because it has a lot of my personal characteristics
and many things I have said before
are all in it
So she is a very thoughtful girl
At that moment, receiving the painting, I felt very touched
This is also one of the
most special gifts I have received in the past two years
Thank you
With a group of new friends
in such a warm big house
performing our own show to celebrate the New Year
It feels very meaningful
and very happy
Five, four, three, two, one
Happy New Year
In 2025,
I hope to find a
place where I truly want to settle down.
I hope to meet someone
who understands and knows me.
And then walk through life together.
I hope in 2025
I can become a more relaxed person.
I hope the new year won't be so lonely.
I always thought I had lost interest in fireworks.
It seemed like I couldn't get excited about them anymore.
But when we went to set off fireworks,
Kaka suddenly
started jumping around.
I suddenly felt like
I was back in my childhood.
It felt a bit magical to watch.
Being able to share this moment with her
was very joyful.
I hope we will get along more comfortably.
Although the two of us
can't celebrate the New Year together
I still want
to see her on the first day of the New Year
happy
very happy
I feel that being with this group
is very meaningful
very interesting
very wonderful
Alright, let's go inside
There are pirates (barrels) here
and prepared
Truth or Dare cards to draw
lean back
it's none of my business
Teacher Hou is so cute
You can draw two cards too
Try it first
Let's see what it is
Draw one card
See what tricky questions it has
So
How, let's see
how difficult
at this level
Choose a person of the opposite sex
This is too exaggerated
Complete a weighted squat
Xiao Jie should be good at this
But the person who wants him to do the squat isn't here
Yes
This card is not bad
Alright, come on, let's start.
Fix it up.
Who starts first?
Come on.
What are you afraid of?
Just go up and strike.
Xiao Jie.
Okay.
Come on, Wanwan
Newcomer benefits
Choose this one
Take one home to marry, is there?
Choose a member of the opposite sex
Complete the weighted squats
So thrilling
Weighted squats
Guess who he will choose
I think
Kaka
Right?
Then I am duty-bound to handle this for Brother Wan
I'll choose the one next to me
Kaka
What does squat mean
How should I cooperate with you
Just stand there
Stand there
Like this
The idol drama is online
Yes
The main point is that Xiao Hu has made
the most thrilling scream since the show started
Yes, finally there are big emotions
Yes, big emotions have finally arrived
Princess carry
Help
It's already 2025
I still scream over things like this
How does it feel to be lifted by a strong man?
It almost killed me.
My face turned red.
What should I do? I'm so happy watching this.
You blushed too.
Yes.
That punishment tonight
is actually quite bold.
It makes you feel a bit
secretly delighted.
You have to choose a member of the opposite sex to do an activity.
Actually, everyone secretly wants to find
someone they are interested in.
to do this.
So this is a
big test point of the game.
Finally discovered the true meaning of this game.
They actually want to lose, right?
Yes.
This should be the dare, right?
We should choose truth.
and then ask.
Then I will definitely choose dare.
Just choose dare.
I also choose dare.
Continue.
I don't want to choose anything.
Don't want to choose anything.
Come on.
Bro.
Xiao Hu, where you sit counts.
He's going to do that.
Come back quickly, Xiao Hu.
What photos are you posting?
So slow
Insert two
Teacher Su wants to play a game
Look
At the moment it bounced up, the corners of the mouth lifted
Happy
Let me read it
Choose a person of the opposite sex to drink a toast with
Crazy, really crazy.
Pour the water first.
Drink the cross-cup water.
Big cross-cup or small cross-cup?
Professional, bro.
Professional.
Can you play this with me?
Sis Tian's terrified look, right.
What did Xiao Hu miss again?
I like having you by my side like this.
You come, come.
Afraid of you, come.
How to drink, come.
How to drink.
Drink like this.
Come, drink like this.
Three, two, one, go.
Teacher, I can't be next to you, teacher
You're too scary
I chased after you
Do you remember that bad joke, Teacher Luo?
What is it?
He said I chased after you
She runs, he chases, she can't escape
Alright, this works
You insert a few, I insert a few
Okay
Do you dare to start with twenty?
Teacher Luo really wears his heart on his sleeve
I want to speak, I want to show off
Let's just play a big adventure game
Just draw cards, you guys
Then let's play something
Something intense, right?
Intense
Soon we'll have to press our feet
Stop inserting
I'm not trying to be strong
Scary
This man's inexplicable desire to win
What's going on
I'm a bit scared
Inexplicable
Male competition
I'll just weakly join in
You guys play your own game
It's not my turn
That's it
Goodbye
I'm scared
Four rounds
It's just four rounds
What's so difficult about it
It doesn't matter
Impossible
Four rounds are just a small matter
Okay
Keep a good mindset
I'll give you one
Brother will give you one
Are you going for three rounds too?
One round is enough for me.
Is it this one?
One, two, three, right?
There's another one here.
There's another one behind.
Four, right?
Okay.
You insert a few, I'll insert a few.
One.
Brother
How many are left?
There are two left.
Brother
These are the last two.
That's not him (Zhang Chenxi)
It's him (Su Yonghao)
One strike to the throat, Brother, go!
It's Su Nan again
Yes, there's one last round
This is a certain death situation
Is this true?
This is true
Teacher, don't
It's too scary
Xiao Hu is going to cry
Is Xiao Hu unable to sit in?
Let's move a bit more this way
Let's move this way
Look, Liang Tian's sitting position is clearly closer to Xiao Hu
What is this?
Read it out
Choose a person of the opposite sex to tie hands with
Until the next person to be punished appears
Come, experience it
Come, tie it up, come
The little fan is being used
All the interesting things have been done by you, brother
Their heads are so close
This body language
He's jealous of you
Look at his expression
I'm not jealous
I'm openly envious
Yonghao expresses his feelings
Actually, it's quite obvious
In the game, they always team up with Liang Tian
You stab a few times, I stab a few times
Double
What are you doing?
Xiao Hu is making a move.
Go for it, Xiao Hu.
Teacher.
It's too scary.
And also,
Four have already been inserted.
Five.
Scary.
Let Xiao Hu get one.
I also want to lose.
But,
My luck is too good.
Scared to "death."
Come.
Eat some sunflower seeds, come.
You eat sunflower seeds.
Choose a member of the opposite sex.
Compare the size of your hands.
My old crush.
Old crush.
Feel it.
Come.
Electric shock.
Heart is moved.
I was actually quite anxious at that moment.
It's just that,
Because I think,
Games like this are a kind of expression.
It's over.
Baby
I just feel like I want to play with Liang Tian
Poke the other person's face
Slap
Slap the other person's face
Brother, I have to do this
Like this
Poke
It's my turn, right?
Go
Just draw a card
Xiao Hu is our spokesperson
Let Xiao Hu take a turn
He's too bored
He's even cracking sunflower seeds
A dramatic swipe, come on
The opportunity is coming your way
Really?
Yes, really
Finally
The opportunity has come
Choose a person of the opposite sex
Cover her eyes from behind for ten seconds
What is
the meaning of this?
It means you have to stand behind her
and cover her eyes like this
then cover them for ten seconds
Hehehe
Then there are three more "hehehe" sounds
Do we really need the "hehehe"?
Then I'll fool you
Fool you
Sis Tian's feeling at this moment
is completely different
Then I'll take off my glasses
Look
Very self-aware
Isn't this already fooling you
One, two, three
Hey
Hehehe, hey
He used this laugh to bring out the laughter in his heart
Happy now
Zero
Good
So funny
Come on, continue
Do it
Forget it, I'll leave it to you.
I'll just stand next to you.
Okay
Choose a member of the opposite sex to put on the accessory for him.
Come on, Liang Tian
Come on
Let's take a look
bracelet
glasses
earrings
I think it's possible
My little earring is quite cute
Then choose one of the opposite sex to wear it
Ear piercing
Only my brother has ear piercings, right?
No
I have
I have two ear piercings
I have one
This is too chaotic
They sat on my left and right
all night
on my left and right
I'm really afraid of putting pressure on others, you know?
It's this kind of
feeling that there might be some direction or something
Of course, I would expect a bit more
interaction with Liang Tian
I think both Liang Tian and I are quite
concerned about everyone's feelings
No matter what decision Liang Tian makes
I think
what I need to do actually remains unchanged
just accept it like this
Who will she poke?
I think she will choose Xiao Hu
Come on
Look at her smile
It seems like only I have ear piercings, right?
I have them too
You do
Not as good-looking as yours
Actually, I already felt it from that moment
Liang Tian towards Hu Yunting
actually had a bit of affection
She ultimately chose me
I was a bit surprised she would be so obvious
to make this move in front of everyone
I think this is her way of signaling
So being chosen is joyful
Okay
Quite good-looking
So beautiful
Can you turn your neck
Just like that
So happy
Look, the way you look at him is different
Your gaze is full of affection
Yes
Choosing Yunting was just at that moment
I just really wanted to play with him
There wasn't any particular reason
Because deep down, I knew who I wanted to play with
I was very clear about it
Cute
I really don't want to see Su Yonghao's disappointed expression
Then let's draw all of them
We can draw directly too
How about we speed up a bit
Choose a person of the opposite sex to feed her a fruit
Come on, Sis
Now, the two of us
We need to look at each other
And we can't laugh
Whoever laughs first has to say "I'm a pig"
Are you ready?
Okay
Come on
Eating an orange is so difficult
This game is too good for me
Teacher Hou, the excitement doesn't belong to him
Actually, it was already quite late at that time
She didn't return to the cabin
So, the mood was a bit down at that time
I couldn't really
participate in the game
I wasn't in the mood to play the game
Do you need help to put it back?
Put it back on again
This isn't one of the big adventures, right?
Give and take
Choose a person of the opposite sex to apply hand cream for her
Really
So much service tonight
I feel like I'm doing a manicure
Manicurist
Come and do some hand care for you
Choose a person of the opposite sex to form a circle with their hands
Let the other person enter the circle
Hold him tight
Let's pack up our things.
Pack up.
The secret date is about to start.
It's scheduled.
Friends,
This time it's secure.
This time it's easy to guess.
Why don't we all check our phones?
What's up?
Is it that serious?
What does it mean?
What should I do?
I think it's too difficult to find this person.
I don't know either.
Even if I find him,
what should I say to him?
When I received this invitation message,
I felt that
it's too unfriendly for introverted people.
Especially in front of so many people.
If you get rejected,
it would be very embarrassing.
There's always a voice in my head
telling me
to be brave and give it a try.
If the invitation is unsuccessful,
I won't have another chance.
I hope I don't miss this opportunity.
The moment I received the dating rules,
I was still a bit conflicted.
Didn't watch enough
This New Year's Eve
Was so joyful
Yes
So funny
We were separated by the screen
But it felt
Like we joined them
Yes
Even Chun Ye wants to play
Quick, bring the cards
Do you want me to help you put on your earrings too?
Yes.
Please help me put them on.
I'll do it.
If I'm going to "die," I want to join a game.
How about it?
Your cards didn't arrive.
I started playing my game first.
I'm excited.
Come into my arms quickly.
Alright.
Let me share something first
Some observations I just made
Details that might go unnoticed by everyone
Yes
I noticed you were taking notes
About Yonghao playing the guitar earlier
Because I also play the guitar
Improvising guitar accompaniment for others
Is actually a very difficult thing to do
When he played for Kaka
He used a capo
Which indicates Kaka also wanted a key change
Using a capo means no need for practice
He can directly switch to that key
And for Liang Tian
Liang Tian
He practiced
Played directly in the lower position
That requires time to practice
Such great details
Love is in the details
So there is a difference
So which one did he spend more time on
It's very obvious
Nailed this detail
The capo really
You are like Leeuwenhoek
Look at this
Yonghao is really attentive.
Yes.
And then there's Liang Tian.
I think Liang Tian is because
of her role as a host.
She usually has to take care of others.
It's a habit.
This time she finally gave herself
some space.
But when she gave herself space,
most of the time she was actually interacting with Xiao Hu.
They were interacting together.
She wasn't paying attention to others.
Yes.
I noticed
that when Liang Tian interacts with Su Yonghao,
when they interact,
she has a lot to say.
For example,
what are you afraid of, or rather,
Yes, like this
This bow, just this feeling
Yes
Just her appearance, this awkwardness
I think it's just one reason
That is to say, in this scene
She has someone she clearly cares about
So because he is also present
I don't want him to feel uncomfortable
Yes
Last time, we couldn't see
What Liang Tian's inclination was
Yes
Today, the inclination is quite clear
I think what moved Sis Tian
Was last time, though late, he arrived
Yes
When he had one kilometer left
He came running
Actually, in Sis Tian's heart
It added a lot of points
Yes, but after that
She wasn't trying to confirm her feelings
She went to find Su Yonghao
Yes
Met once
Had a date
Concert, yes
And now she's back again
Xiao Hu wasn't shaken by this
And clearly expressed his feelings
Yes
He can say "I want to play with you"
And say "I want to lose"
Then he inserted five times in a row
These actions are quite proactive
But just now Yixin mentioned a point
Later, these boys understood the game
The purpose of this game is to lose
Only by losing can there be interaction
Yes
But I think if it is
Two people who might have feelings for each other
These little thoughts in a relationship
Or what we call "little tricks"
Actually, it's quite a cute behavior
Yes
In the process of your relationship
You or your friends
Have there been moments like this
Where you proactively create
Little opportunities
My "scheme" fits perfectly
with this matter
My "scheme" is about New Year's Eve
because every New Year's Eve
I can't spend it with my loved ones
because I'm hosting the New Year's Eve event
Yes
During the countdown to midnight
there's always a segment
to share your New Year's wishes
For example, this year I said
I hope next year
we can continue to explore the world together
Actually, these words are for the listeners
who don't really know what I'm talking about
but the recipient clearly understands
The audience says
I was just a part of your game
I thought you were blessing me
but you had a hidden meaning
No, just a little "trick" at the end
So every year before midnight
I always send it to my family
and to my loved one
It's actually a double entendre
A double entendre, yes
Every sentence doesn't mention "I love you"
but every sentence means "I love you"
Yes, that's the meaning
I find it very touching
This point especially touches me
Really?
Yes, exactly
That kind of subtle hint
Yes
Subtle hints are more impactful than explicit ones
Like when I directly tell you
Next year, let's see the world together
It feels more meaningful
Find me
Next year, I'll take you to see the world
Your internet speed is also very fast.
Say it directly to my face.
So, what kind of "little tricks" do you like?
Secretive "little tricks."
Have you experienced this kind?
I really haven't experienced it much.
Because my experience is
more direct.
Just express whatever directly.
Maybe it's because
you haven't encountered this kind now.
But if you change the style,
if he is like this,
you might need him to be more straightforward.
Yes.
So, everything has a limit.
This is actually quite good, yes.
Life can't be that perfect.
I found that Guangguang is very
sensitive about emotional topics.
He actually considers many angles.
He thinks from a woman's perspective.
That's impressive.
No.
In the previous scene,
there was also
something we mentioned at the beginning,
which is the atmosphere of a friends' gathering.
So you would feel that
this group of people being together
is very lovely.
It's such unrestrained happiness.
And in this,
you slowly discover
the feelings you might be looking for.
What exactly they are.
The gathering scene just now
was quite touching for me.
I wonder if it made you think of
a time or a few times
when you were with friends
and had this kind of feeling.
Actually, regarding New Year's Eve
over the years, it has gradually become
a few members of the "Reemployment Boy Band"
the guys would team up to take on the New Year's Eve gala
0713's
Yes
What impressed me the most was actually
our Spring Festival Gala this year
we were the second performance
I watched it
and during our second performance
we said, brothers, this year we finally
can eat dumplings
because last year
we were in the middle performance
so we didn't get to
eat dumplings on New Year's Eve
and that day we were especially happy
actually, when you are with good friends
gathering together
you will be happy about
some very small things
even happier than performing at the Spring Festival Gala
because all of us
really want to perform at the Spring Festival Gala
after performing
but that night
if we could also eat those dumplings
it would be perfect
if these people are right beside you
then you will feel
today is amazing
how can it be this amazing
you will feel
next year I want to perform at the Spring Festival Gala again
I still want to eat dumplings
I have to eat dumplings
Yes, exactly
I have a New Year's Eve
particularly unforgettable experience
What is it?
It was one New Year's Eve
by Lake Baikal
in a small cabin hotel
This name is a winner
Yes
There was a lot of snow, thick and soft
The cabins were covered in snow
Very beautiful, very romantic
Then we finished eating at the restaurant
and walked to the cabin
While walking, suddenly
He discovered
the ring on his hand was missing.
Then that ring
was our couple ring at the time
but we planned to use it
as the ring to exchange at our wedding
so it was essentially our wedding ring
It was very important, he said it was missing
It was over minus twenty degrees at the time
He went to the restaurant to look for it
He searched for a long time but couldn't find it
Then I said
Did you check your pocket?
Look again
It was amazing
His clothes pocket
had a hole inside
right in the inner layer
Yes, he was very happy
You know, he said he felt it
Then he took it out
The moment he took it out, it was amazing
As soon as he took it out, it fell
Because the snow was very soft
the moment you fell in, you disappeared
I watched you fall
no matter how hard I looked, I couldn't find you
I searched for a long time and was freezing
eventually, we all gave up
I also had that ring on my hand
so I conducted an experiment
from the same height, and then dropped it
to see how deep it was
then I searched again
I randomly picked a spot
also nearby
and threw it like this
sure enough
the moment it fell, it disappeared
then I dug it up and picked it up
then something magical happened
right next to it
the ring was right next to it
yes
Destiny
If this were a TV drama
I would think the screenwriter is making things up
Yes
But it happened in real life
Destined to be together
Is this fate?
Everything has to be just right
So at the moment you found it
Did you both feel a certain
Feeling of some kind
Really felt that it was fate
It was beyond words, that kind of
Tears of joy
This is so romantic
This is so amazing
Really
So I think life is always
more exciting than TV dramas
Yes
Indeed
This is truly amazing
Yangyang, do you have
anything to share?
Maybe not that much sense of ceremony
Maybe haven't had the chance
to create something like that
But losing the ring, next time
But about the ring
I'm really angry about the ring
Because we also have a ring
He lost his
Yes
It was also a couple's ring
Still haven't found it
Maybe it's
I'm "furious"
I need to lose something
Yes
Me too
Maybe need to do some experiment
Yes
And so when I just heard
I felt it was particularly amazing
Yes
But when it comes to gatherings, it's really just okay
I'm the kind of person who is relatively plain
And the pursuit of a sense of ceremony
Is not particularly strong
He is too
So the two of us together are quite
Able to get along and live together
Like last year
Our New Year's Eve concert ended
Then we celebrated the New Year in the car
And I was also watching the countdown
The only sense of ceremony was
Watching the clock hit midnight
Then recording a short video saying
Happy New Year
And then it was over
It feels like if you keep talking, it will become
Brother Tao's roast session a bit
But the two of us feel very comfortable
Yes, there's no burden
I've seen your video
Brother Tao made a show himself
And at the end of the show, he went to propose
Yes
At that time, I almost went
Yes, he was invited
He seemed to have something going on at that time
Yes, that was me
The most ceremonial scene for me
Did you really not know on the spot?
I had guessed
There were some small surprises
But I didn't guess it was this surprise
If we mention now
the most surprising thing for you
the most ceremonial thing for you
I would still picture that scene
Moreover, that scene
everyone's blessings
friends' blessings are also there
yes
are all around, right?
right
I just heard everyone
sharing their sense of ceremony
when recalling a memory
Actually, life is long and ordinary
That sense of ceremony is actually
something we create for ourselves in our ordinary lives
something we create for ourselves
some memory points
These memory points
Whoever shares these memory points with you
this person in these memory points
is immortal
Yes
This connection is very lasting
Maybe we
like these ordinary guests
being together
our connection is not that close
but after such a
shared sense of ceremony
there will be an emotional projection
that I was at that
very memorable memory point
I once shared with this person
So with others
whether friends or lovers
having shared some
ceremonial moments
is very precious
Yes
Refining in memory
Right
Purified some shining memories
We need to
highlight some key points in life
There was another person highlighting key points with me
A group of people highlighted this key point for me
We are together at this moment
We created some
extraordinary sentiments in the ordinary
and then added some heavy colors
How deep is this memory
The projection of this emotion is very strong
It will definitely have an impact on their emotions
and provide good guidance
Yes
So in the upcoming
if they choose to have a secret date
during the process
perhaps during this gathering just now
the interactions between everyone
will have some impact
There will definitely be an effect
There definitely will be
So should we guess
what the final match of their secret date will be
what kind of match it will be
Yes
Let's move on to today's
Soul's True Moment
Let's guess
which pairs can secretly
succeed in their date
just guess correctly
Yes
It's like knocking on the door
If it doesn't work, just ignore it
Global beauty and health products
Search for Watsons mini program on WeChat
Delivered in as fast as thirty minutes
Please watch Watsons' sincere reasoning moment
They might have that kind of...
Anyway, we didn't make it
Let's team up and have some fun
That kind of situation
It's possible, I think it's possible
Yes
Is it ready?
It's ready.
Show the question board.
Come on, Teacher Du
I think Yun Ting and Liang Tian might work
Yes
We think so too
Guo Guo will come back, right?
Yes, Guo Guo is participating
I think Guo Guo might come back
Xiao Hou might be with her
Yes, Teacher Hou and Guo Guo are locked in
They are mutually committed
It's truly a rare life experience
Yes, I think they are both very sincere people
They give to each other and appreciate each other
I think you must be their true fan
I really am
This is what we are most certain about
There's also Wan Xiao and Kaka
Yes, I also chose Wan Xiao and Kaka
Because during New Year's
There was a detail about squatting
And Wan Xiao chose to do it while holding Kaka
Wan Xiao and Kaka
Yes
I think Kaka will definitely go
Invite Su Yonghao
But actually, I have a different idea from you
I have a different idea
Wan Xiao actually sent signals
That night
And I felt
Kaka received them
So I think
These two pairs are likely stable
This pair is possible
Come on, teammates.
Kaka is definitely going to find Yonghao.
Because that night,
the situation between Xiao Hu and Liang Tian
was too obvious.
So I think Yonghao
might accept Kaka.
There's another pair I think
Luo Junfan and Yan Xing might
I'm exactly like the teacher
Me too
I think this season compared to previous ones
is very different in that
at this stage, it seems more
everyone has a more open mindset
These two pairs
I think they also have that mindset
So you two are exactly the same
Yes, our answers are the same
But the attitude in judging it is different
But it doesn't matter
Then Teacher Du and I
are the same as Yiyang
And me
You're the same as us too
On the Soul app
meet interesting souls who understand you
Next, we enter
the Soul's true reveal moment
In the end, Liang Tian chose that Su Yonghao.
Impossible.
Liang Tian said before
that she had already seen the sun.
But the moon,
she only saw a bit through the clouds.
Encounter around the corner
I have something to ask you
Tomorrow night
Do you want to go on a date with me?
I miss you
Okay
Xiao Hu
They are still sneaking around
Sneaking around
Acting suspiciously
Still sneaking around
Why?
It's quite thrilling
When I received the secret notice
I had already decided in my mind
I want to ask Liang Tian out again
It feels very sneaky
Secretly
I was originally considering whether to directly
Ask her if she could go out with me
But I was afraid it would be too obvious
Then everyone would know
Teacher Liang, if you're fine, just go to sleep
You're still not feeling well
Okay
I realized
I should leave this room first
So I went towards
The stairwell on the second floor
He anticipated it
So impressive
It's quite thrilling
Looking forward to it
Even Xiao Hu can do this
Chose a corner for the location
It's the corner of love
"Little tricks"
Who did love meet at the corner
The moon met at the corner
I'll go help clean up again
I see you have arranged a meeting with Tian Tian.
A man who realizes things late.
Still continuing?
I have an appointment.
It's okay.
It really is
I was clearly feeling so happy just a moment ago
Going out to play with Yunting
Then after being rejected
I have mixed feelings
My guilt
suddenly surged up
No need to sweep
Go to sleep
I'll sweep tomorrow
I'll have time tomorrow
Stop working.
Really, stop working.
You're still not well, okay?
Stop working.
Really, stop working.
Take a rest.
I'll help you sweep.
Go to sleep.
You know I'm used to it.
This is too painful.
Actually, there is a sense of guilt inside for rejecting others.
I really am
I should go outside and sit for a while
and get some fresh air
You're back
I bought some food for you
Dried strawberries
Thank you
Let me do it
It's okay
Thank you
Should we take our medicine tonight?
Take the medicine.
He always remembers everything she said.
He remembers all the things he needs to do.
Are you okay?
What are you thinking about?
I'm fine.
I
I just feel
I feel really bad when I reject others.
I don't want to hurt others.
But I don't want to go against my own feelings.
But I think this issue
I need to process it myself.
It's my guilt
and my true feelings.
They can't be mixed together.
They need to be viewed separately.
But not because you feel guilty.
I know.
So I feel really happy.
I'm really looking forward to tomorrow's date.
I'm looking forward to it too.
January 1st.
The first day.
The first night.
Very happy.
I think it's okay.
One person understands at a time.
What is Kaka doing?
Heading towards Su.
What's going on?
Actually, because I also expressed
I have always had feelings for Su Yonghao
the most positive feelings.
I just want to say
that at that moment, I might have
felt more uncomfortable about not being brave
than the feeling of being timid and afraid of trouble.
If she feels
that if she doesn't initiate this invitation,
she will feel very uncomfortable.
She will feel uncomfortable.
Because usually,
I think I am quite generous.
At that moment, I really wanted to say
let's be brave for once.
So,
how about a date tomorrow?
Sure.
Okay.
Yonghao,
okay.
He said okay.
That went smoothly.
Yes, so we still need to be a bit braver.
What if?
After I finished speaking
I really felt amazing
I finally
in a field I'm not good at
I bravely expressed myself
I managed to take control of this matter
And when I finished expressing myself
I really felt
Taking control feels so good.
Because I really don't reject people much
That kind of thinking
And before that
Because I received her tea leaves
I was moved
Today he also said
He wants to drink tea leaves
I really bought it directly
Isn't this a coincidence, brother?
Her actions really moved me.
We guessed wrong.
We got two pairs wrong.
Look.
Actually, at that time in my heart,
the target I wanted to choose was Kaka.
Then I saw Lao Su
with Kaka, the two of them together.
Talking about things like this
I just guessed
That Kaka might be asked out by Old Su
Then later I thought
Yan Xing just arrived after all
And didn't have many opportunities to interact
I understand
Okay
Then let's meet tomorrow
So later I thought
Let's just choose her to get to know better
Then I was right
I was right
In the end, they became you two
Do you two have some kind of god's perspective?
You have spoilers, right?
"The Yang Di of romance shows"
At that time, I really had no idea.
On one hand, previously I
did indeed have the most dates with Wei.
But I have a feeling
that maybe we were getting too close.
And actually,
this isn't a good thing.
This time,
I'll take a break.
And give her some time and space.
Give up
Yes
Good night then
Good night
So late
Still waiting for someone to get off work.
Pure Love War God
It's because I'm still hesitating
I still have this thought before sleeping
Wondering if I can wait for this person
Just like last time, waiting for her to knock on the door
She will really knock
He hasn't started dating yet
So I'm still a bit nervous
What's up?
What are you doing?
Let me see.
Will Dudu come back later?
She
Why are you still awake?
This timing is really
This timing
Is it really that amazing?
Yes, it's that amazing.
It's really that amazing.
This is too amazing.
Is everyone asleep?
They just went up.
I was playing games just now.
Did you have dinner?
I finished eating.
I had two meals.
Wait for me a moment.
I have a New Year's gift for you.
Really?
Thank you.
I thought I wouldn't see you for New Year.
Because today was really unexpected.
Because I forgot the later schedule.
Otherwise, around eleven o'clock
I could have made it back.
So you
still need to go out, right?
It will take two minutes.
Because my stuff is in the car.
It's not a delay.
It's just that you need to go out.
Or should I go out with you?
Then come with me.
Just take a walk.
Okay, I'll go with you.
There is definitely no problem.
We saved some fireworks for you.
Really?
Tomorrow.
You saved them for me?
Yes.
I didn't expect that.
You would stay so late tonight.
Actually, I didn't expect it to be this late either.
I usually don't stay up this late.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Last time you asked me out,
this time it's possible.
Can I ask you out for a date tomorrow, on New Year's?
Sure.
Yes.
Okay.
You two...
The joy of true fans.
Happy New Year.
Thank you.
Did you taste my sweet macarons?
Soul is interesting
Free encounters
This program is played by young people
Soul APP
Exclusively titled broadcast
Global beauty and health products
On Watsons mini program
Thanks to healthy beauty, beautiful health
Sponsored by Watsons
This is my favorite place
This shot looks great
Today's date with Liang Tian
was actually very happy
I just felt
she was quietly paying attention to me
and cooperating with me
I felt quite happy
We match well
I have interacted with many people
They would give me
the idea that
marriage might be the grave of love
They might have a rather pessimistic attitude
towards their future life
But I think it doesn't affect me at this moment
I still have hopes, right
Yes
Our views on marriage
are aligned
Have we talked this deeply
We've talked this far
Your affection for me only comes from
me giving you tea leaves at that time
Can I understand the tea leaves
as just a gesture of kindness
Yes
Emotion doesn't play any role in your mind
does it
Some are happy, some are sad
Really
Anyway, I lit the firecracker
Is this firecracker loud or silent
I can't try anymore
Kaka is amazing
It's really uncomfortable
It's rare to see Su Yonghao in this state
Yes
This is too much of a battlefield.
President Su is about to take action.
Going alone to the meeting.
Do we have
the possibility afterwards
the thoughts afterwards